aiseesoft.com 2014-11-14

# Aiseesoft Customer Privacy Policy

Aiseesoft Studio is committed to protecting your privacy. Your privacy is a priority at Aiseesoft. We go to great lengths to protect it. This Customer Privacy Policy covers why we collect your personal information, what information we collect, what we use it for and how we protect it.

### Why we collect your personal information?

We collect your personal information because it helps us deliver a superior level of customer service. It enables us to give you convenient access to our products and services and focus on categories of greatest interest to you. In addition, your personal information helps us keep you posted on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers, and events that you might like to hear about.

### What information do we collect? What do we use it for?

When you place an order on our website, your full name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card number, and credit card expiration date will be required. The information is used to complete the transaction and help us provide better support and services to you.

### How we protect your personal information?

Aiseesoft takes precautions — including administrative, technical, and physical measures — to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

Aiseesoft uses secure server hosted by RegNow and other 3rd party credit card processors that encrypt the entire customer's personal information including name, address, credit card number credit card expiration date etc. before it is sent to us. Encryption works to prevent any malicious use of your personal information.

You can help us by also taking precautions to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often using a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure web browser like Safari.

### SWREG

SWREG is an online payment processor that is the best Paypal alternative for global businesses. It offers numerous payment options and currencies, including phone and fax order support in 16 countries. Aiseesoft uses SWREG to make it easier for you to buy products.

### Avangate

Agile eCommerce platform for online software sales trusted by software and Software-as-a-Service companies to sell products via any channel and any model. Aiseesoft uses Avangate to provide a well-defined, seamless ordering and support experience.

### Cookies

In order to better understand what services are valuable to our customers, we use "cookies". A cookie is a small text file that a Website writes to your hard drive. Cookies work as your identification card and may record passwords, preferences and purchases. Cookies let the web page server know that you have returned to this site. Cookies also can determine other information, such as the daily visitors to our web site and the pages of the site most frequently visited. Cookies are unique and can only be read by the server that assigns them. They cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses.

You can change the settings in your browser to prevent cookies if you do not want to have a cookie set when you visit our website. However, by doing so, you may not have full access to all the web pages.
